<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Blessed Tutorial</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="image_size">98dp</string>
    <string name="about_us">ABOUT US
\n\"Education is bail out of ignorance"
Blessed academy is an organization that is so passionate about an effective
delivery in teaching and to bring about reformation in the academic sector in
Nigeria and in the world at large.
\n\Based on recent research and experience we have come to realize
that the level of education is diminishing day by day while the number of
school is increasing on a daily basis without effective methods of teaching
and impacting into the life of these students.\n\Old methods of teaching are
still commonly used in various schools around and we  thought of a solution
to this incidence.\n\Thereby coming up with this idea to:
\n\ Promote the standard of education
\n\ Introduce the 21st century means of education
\n\ Review syllabus
\n\ Reach out to millions of students on our platform
\n\ Give recent information to schools and teachers on recent research in
their subjects
\n\ Making learning easier and accommodating for all.
\n\We believe with the help of God and our relentless effort,we will be
able to reach out to students and reform the educational system in Nigeria
and the world at large.</string>
    <string name="about">ABOUT US Education is bail out of ignorance Blessed academy is an organization that is so passionate about an effective delivery in teaching and to bring about reformation in the academic sector in Nigeria and in the world at large. Based on recent research and experience we have come to realize that the level of education is diminishing day by day while the number of school is increasing on a daily basis without effective methods of teaching and impacting into the life of these students.Old methods of teaching are still commonly used in various schools around and we thought of a solution to this incidence.Thereby coming up with this idea to:  Promote the standard of education  Introduce the 21st century means of education  Review syllabus  Reach out to millions of students on our platform  Give recent information to schools and teachers on recent research in their subjects  Making learning easier and accommodating for all. We believe with the help of God and our relentless effort,we will be able to reach out to students and reform the educational system in Nigeria and the world at large.</string>


</resources>
